OLKOWSKA-DWILEWICZ DOROTA

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

HELLO,

I am a graphic designer by education and profession with a specialisation in commercial design. I fell in love with graphic design in 2013 and have been doing it professionally for over 7 years. TTL's marketing have no secrets for me, I find myself in a wide range of graphic design. I don't like to treat design in a standard way, so I take an individual approach to each project. Now I am developing in UX and UI design under the supervision of a mentor.

EDUCATION

2013 – 2016 WARSAW SCHOOL OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (WIT), WARSAW

Specialisation: Commercial Design Certificate: Bachelor's degree

EXPERIENCE

2022 - CURRENTLY GRAPHIC DESIGNER

SMG AGENCY, BIALYSTOK

Close work with the IT department to develop websites for products, design and prepress of products, graphic design of BTL marketing, creation of DTP materials for the company, graphic support for the company as needed.

2019 - 2021 GRAPHIC DESIGNER

EQUALAN PHARMA EUROPE, BIALYSTOK

Design and prepress of products (i.a. Novaclear, Regital), graphic design of TTL marketing, product photography, creation of DTP materials, graphic support for the company as needed.

2018 - 2019 GRAPHIC DESIGNER

EFIRST GROUP, WARSAW

Cooperation with the IT department (web design according to UI/UX, graphic support), design and prepress of products for the Asian market, visualization of products, graphic design of BTL marketing, creation of DTP materials for the company.

CONTACT

- 508 962 074
- olkowskadorota@gmail.com
- dorotaolkowska.github.io/-/
- Bialystok, Poland

SKILLS

After Effects

Photoshop Advanced
Illustrator Advanced

InDesign Advanced

Intermediate

Dreamweaver Intermediate

Figma Intermediate

UX Beginner

UI Beginner

HTML Beginner

CSS Beginner

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate

EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2018 GRAPHIC DESIGNER

MYGIFTDNA, WARSAW

Graphic support for the customers, contact with clients, graphic design of BTL marketing, creation of mockups and visualization of products, design of new products in terms of machine guidelines (laser engraving, embroidery, plotter, sublimation, DTG digital printing, printing on canvas), operation of a 3D printer, graphic support for the company as needed.

2016 GRAPHIC DESIGNER

ALZAHRANI INTERNATIONAL HOLDING GROUP, WARSAW

Design and prepress of magazines, creation of DTP materials, graphic support for the company as needed.

FREELANCE (some)

2021 - CURRENTLY GRAPHIC DESIGNER

DOBRY GUCIO!, BIALYSTOK

Branding and TTL marketing design (graphic and copywrite).

2021 - CURRENTLY GRAPHIC DESIGNER

SŁOMIANA PRACOWNIA, BIALYSTOK

Products series design, graphic support.

2019 - 2020 GRAPHIC DESIGNER

GREAT HOUSE, BIALYSTOK

Company's logo design, graphic support.

2017 GRAPHIC DESIGNER

INSTITUTE OF HEALTH, WARSAW

Company's logo and products design, creating DTP materials.

2013 - CURRENTLY GRAPHIC DESIGNER

LA VENDOWY SALON, LOMZA

Branding, creating DTP materials, design of BTL marketing.

INTERESTS

- Board games
- Italian cuisine
- Aquaristics

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).